=My Rich Little Brother=
= أخي الغني الصغير =
=Episode 12=
= الحلقة 12 =
Who is it?
من هذا؟
It's me.
هذا أنا.
Zhengzheng.
Zhengzheng.
Have a seat.
تفضل بالجلوس.
I'm cooking.
انا أطبخ.
Zhengzheng.
Zhengzheng.
You...
أنت...
What are you wearing?
ماذا ترتدي؟
Let me see.
دعني أرى.
Are you wearing your dad's clothes?
هل ترتدي ملابس والدك؟
Here. Have a seat.
هنا.  تفضل بالجلوس.
Have some water.
اشرب بعض الماء.
Is there anything you want to eat?
هل هناك أي شيء تريد أن تأكله؟
I'm cooking.
انا أطبخ.
You're a kid.
أنت طفل.
Why are you bringing flowers over?
لماذا تحضر الزهور؟
I'm not a kid anymore.
أنا لست طفلا بعد الآن.
You're not a kid anymore.
لم تعد طفلاً.
What are you then?
ماذا انت اذن
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Don't pat me on the head.
لا تربت على رأسي.
You don't get it at all.
أنت لا تحصل عليه على الإطلاق.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
You're not a kid anymore.
لم تعد طفلاً.
Well then,
حسنا اذن،
let's do something
دعنا نفعل شيئا ما
that adults do.
الذي يفعله الكبار.
Something that adults do?
شيء يفعله الكبار؟
It's really
إنها حقا
my first time.
اول مره لي.
I can't do it very well yet.
لا أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك جيدًا حتى الآن.
It's fine.
لا بأس.
I'll teach you.
سوف اعلمك.
Here.
هنا.
Take off your clothes.
اخلع ملابسك.
Put on the apron.
ارتدي المريلة.
- Watch out for the oil. - Sister.
- احترس من الزيت.  - أخت.
I burned it.
لقد أحرقته.
It happens.
يحدث ذلك.
Add some water.
أضف بعض الماء.
Fine.
بخير.
Go and answer the door, Zhengzheng.
اذهب وأجب على الباب ، Zhengzheng.
Come here, Sister.
تعالي هنا ، أختاه.
I'll answer the door.
سأجيب على الباب.
- You...
- أنت ... - أنت ...
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
I should be asking you this question.
يجب أن أسألك هذا السؤال.
Mr. Wei.
السيد وي.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
I...
أنا...
As the chairman of the company,
بصفته رئيس مجلس إدارة الشركة ،
I wanted to check on my employees' daily life.
كنت أرغب في التحقق من الحياة اليومية لموظفيي.
Does every chairman bring flowers
هل كل رئيس يجلب الزهور
when they check on their employees?
عندما يقومون بفحص موظفيهم؟
Wow.
رائع.
So beautiful.
جميلة جدا.
Is something burning?
هل هناك شيء يحترق؟
I'll turn off the stove.
سأطفئ الموقد.
Let me.
دعني.
Mr. Wei,
السيد وي ،
you shouldn't do such things.
لا يجب أن تفعل مثل هذه الأشياء.
I didn't know you are a good cook.
لم أكن أعرف أنك طباخة ماهرة.
Enjoy.
يتمتع.
I'm warning you,
أنا أحذرك،
don't you try for my sister.
لا تحاول لأختي.
Your sister
أختك
is really a good girl.
هي حقا فتاة جيدة.
Since you've always liked her so much,
بما أنك كنت تحبها كثيرًا دائمًا ،
why don't I take her home and marry her,
لماذا لا آخذها للمنزل وأتزوجها ،
so she can be your sister-in-law?
حتى تكون أخت زوجتك؟
♪I worry if you'd get nervous♪
♪ أنا قلق إذا شعرت بالتوتر ♪
(Next episode) I like Wei Yingying.
(الحلقة التالية) أحب وي ينجينج.
Since we were kids,
منذ أن كنا أطفالًا ،
I never competed with you for anything
أنا لم أتنافس معك من أجل أي شيء
that you liked.
الذي اعجبك.
From now on,
من الان فصاعدا،
I'll be the one that protects you.
سأكون من يحميك.
♪The shadows stretch long over time♪
تمتد الظلال لفترة طويلة مع مرور الوقت ♪
♪We can't let go♪
♪ لا يمكننا تركه ♪